{
  "inputTimeWaitSecs": 60,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "8703 + 4290",
      "answer": "12993"
    },
    {
      "question": "3594 + 1943",
      "answer": "5537"
    },
    {
      "question": "4371 + 6660",
      "answer": "11031"
    },
    {
      "question": "5231 + 1552",
      "answer": "6783"
    },
    {
      "question": "2464 + 7410",
      "answer": "9874"
    },
    {
      "question": "6196 + 2250",
      "answer": "8446"
    },
    {
      "question": "4857 + 9163",
      "answer": "14020"
    },
    {
      "question": "4962 + 6683",
      "answer": "11645"
    },
    {
      "question": "1531 + 120",
      "answer": "1651"
    },
    {
      "question": "5579 + 3765",
      "answer": "9344"
    },
    {
      "question": "3714 + 3764",
      "answer": "7478"
    },
    {
      "question": "5402 + 4097",
      "answer": "9499"
    },
    {
      "question": "2411 + 4420",
      "answer": "6831"
    },
    {
      "question": "1158 + 4218",
      "answer": "5376"
    },
    {
      "question": "1527 + 1647",
      "answer": "3174"
    },
    {
      "question": "1811 + 6488",
      "answer": "8299"
    },
    {
      "question": "9253 + 5570",
      "answer": "14823"
    },
    {
      "question": "9812 + 7543",
      "answer": "17355"
    },
    {
      "question": "9854 + 6913",
      "answer": "16767"
    },
    {
      "question": "293 + 4069",
      "answer": "4362"
    },
    {
      "question": "2066 + 6981",
      "answer": "9047"
    },
    {
      "question": "9356 + 4490",
      "answer": "13846"
    },
    {
      "question": "7138 + 8440",
      "answer": "15578"
    },
    {
      "question": "3858 + 4524",
      "answer": "8382"
    },
    {
      "question": "8736 + 3498",
      "answer": "12234"
    },
    {
      "question": "3404 + 1806",
      "answer": "5210"
    },
    {
      "question": "6809 + 4258",
      "answer": "11067"
    },
    {
      "question": "3838 + 4197",
      "answer": "8035"
    },
    {
      "question": "7777 + 5856",
      "answer": "13633"
    },
    {
      "question": "9546 + 5935",
      "answer": "15481"
    },
    {
      "question": "7915 + 7684",
      "answer": "15599"
    },
    {
      "question": "6200 + 5746",
      "answer": "11946"
    },
    {
      "question": "736 + 9639",
      "answer": "10375"
    },
    {
      "question": "1767 + 8154",
      "answer": "9921"
    },
    {
      "question": "7162 + 754",
      "answer": "7916"
    },
    {
      "question": "6538 + 6452",
      "answer": "12990"
    },
    {
      "question": "4231 + 578",
      "answer": "4809"
    },
    {
      "question": "3998 + 1164",
      "answer": "5162"
    },
    {
      "question": "9415 + 4633",
      "answer": "14048"
    },
    {
      "question": "3432 + 2245",
      "answer": "5677"
    },
    {
      "question": "807 + 1491",
      "answer": "2298"
    },
    {
      "question": "3579 + 359",
      "answer": "3938"
    },
    {
      "question": "2594 + 9270",
      "answer": "11864"
    },
    {
      "question": "1166 + 6164",
      "answer": "7330"
    },
    {
      "question": "2976 + 9775",
      "answer": "12751"
    },
    {
      "question": "3348 + 4781",
      "answer": "8129"
    },
    {
      "question": "6943 + 6647",
      "answer": "13590"
    },
    {
      "question": "7128 + 5293",
      "answer": "12421"
    },
    {
      "question": "805 + 5162",
      "answer": "5967"
    },
    {
      "question": "8854 + 6908",
      "answer": "15762"
    },
    {
      "question": "2283 + 3881",
      "answer": "6164"
    },
    {
      "question": "3051 + 1059",
      "answer": "4110"
    },
    {
      "question": "9751 + 4077",
      "answer": "13828"
    },
    {
      "question": "8679 + 4951",
      "answer": "13630"
    },
    {
      "question": "3727 + 2931",
      "answer": "6658"
    },
    {
      "question": "6869 + 122",
      "answer": "6991"
    },
    {
      "question": "1835 + 2748",
      "answer": "4583"
    },
    {
      "question": "6696 + 1257",
      "answer": "7953"
    },
    {
      "question": "1460 + 2688",
      "answer": "4148"
    },
    {
      "question": "5210 + 2465",
      "answer": "7675"
    },
    {
      "question": "2088 + 1249",
      "answer": "3337"
    },
    {
      "question": "7238 + 2014",
      "answer": "9252"
    },
    {
      "question": "3837 + 7261",
      "answer": "11098"
    },
    {
      "question": "5281 + 6417",
      "answer": "11698"
    },
    {
      "question": "3889 + 7658",
      "answer": "11547"
    },
    {
      "question": "4026 + 6558",
      "answer": "10584"
    },
    {
      "question": "2206 + 6068",
      "answer": "8274"
    },
    {
      "question": "9901 + 5234",
      "answer": "15135"
    },
    {
      "question": "282 + 1867",
      "answer": "2149"
    },
    {
      "question": "8941 + 4607",
      "answer": "13548"
    },
    {
      "question": "7976 + 9407",
      "answer": "17383"
    },
    {
      "question": "7817 + 3312",
      "answer": "11129"
    },
    {
      "question": "8928 + 2954",
      "answer": "11882"
    },
    {
      "question": "8941 + 7118",
      "answer": "16059"
    },
    {
      "question": "6746 + 8110",
      "answer": "14856"
    },
    {
      "question": "7199 + 869",
      "answer": "8068"
    },
    {
      "question": "8319 + 1430",
      "answer": "9749"
    },
    {
      "question": "8497 + 6823",
      "answer": "15320"
    },
    {
      "question": "1348 + 9856",
      "answer": "11204"
    },
    {
      "question": "2529 + 7885",
      "answer": "10414"
    },
    {
      "question": "6575 + 4244",
      "answer": "10819"
    },
    {
      "question": "3846 + 1665",
      "answer": "5511"
    },
    {
      "question": "6311 + 1028",
      "answer": "7339"
    },
    {
      "question": "5040 + 6270",
      "answer": "11310"
    },
    {
      "question": "6903 + 1140",
      "answer": "8043"
    },
    {
      "question": "1307 + 4225",
      "answer": "5532"
    },
    {
      "question": "8407 + 8527",
      "answer": "16934"
    },
    {
      "question": "7976 + 9823",
      "answer": "17799"
    },
    {
      "question": "4978 + 630",
      "answer": "5608"
    },
    {
      "question": "5940 + 5214",
      "answer": "11154"
    },
    {
      "question": "6800 + 7499",
      "answer": "14299"
    },
    {
      "question": "7939 + 2727",
      "answer": "10666"
    },
    {
      "question": "7594 + 7432",
      "answer": "15026"
    },
    {
      "question": "1744 + 3734",
      "answer": "5478"
    },
    {
      "question": "4545 + 5827",
      "answer": "10372"
    },
    {
      "question": "7495 + 9894",
      "answer": "17389"
    },
    {
      "question": "156 + 2182",
      "answer": "2338"
    },
    {
      "question": "1153 + 8806",
      "answer": "9959"
    },
    {
      "question": "4158 + 7753",
      "answer": "11911"
    },
    {
      "question": "7479 + 7921",
      "answer": "15400"
    }
  ]
}
